<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:php="http://php.net/ns/news">
 <title>PHP 5.3 alpha3 released!</title>
 <id>http://www.php.net/archive/2008.php#id2008-12-04-2</id>
 <published>2008-12-04T17:00:32+01:00</published>
 <updated>2008-12-04T17:00:32+01:00</updated>
 <category term="frontpage" label="PHP.net frontpage news"/>
 <link href="http://www.php.net/index.php#id2008-12-04-2" rel="alternate" type="text/html"/>
 <link href="http://www.php.net/archive/2008.php#id2008-12-04-2" rel="via" type="text/html"/>
 <content type="xhtml">
  <div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
   <p>The PHP development team is proud to announce the <a href="http://qa.php.net/">third alpha release</a>
    of the upcoming PHP 5.3.0 minor version update of PHP.
    Several new features have already been documented in the <a href="http://php.net/docs.php">official documentation</a>,
    others are listed on the <a href="http://wiki.php.net/doc/scratchpad/upgrade/53">wiki</a>
    in preparation of getting documented. It is imperative that more people
    join the effort to complete the documentation for PHP 5.3.0.
    Please also review the <a href="http://php.net/php5news">NEWS</a> file.</p>
   <strong>THIS IS A DEVELOPMENT PREVIEW - DO NOT USE IT IN PRODUCTION!</strong>
   <p>The purpose of this alpha release is to encourage users to not only actively
    participate in identifying bugs, but also in ensuring that all new features or
    necessary backwards compatibility breaks are noted in the documentation. Please
    report any findings to the <a href="mailto:php-qa@lists.php.net">QA mailinglist</a>
    or the <a href="http://bugs.php.net">bug tracker</a>.</p>
   <p>There have been a great number of other additions and improvements since the last alpha,
    but here is a short overview of the most important changes:</p>
   <ul>
    <li><a href="http://php.net/language.namespaces">Namespaces</a> (documentation has been updated to the current state)</li>
    <li>
     <a href="http://wiki.php.net/rfc/rounding">Rounding behavior</a>
    </li>
    <li>ext/msql has been removed, while ext/ereg will now raise E_DEPRECATED notices</li>
    <li>ext/mhash has been replaced by ext/hash but full BC is maintained</li>
    <li>PHP now uses cc as the default compiler, instead of gcc</li>
    <li>A number of bug fixes to ext/pdo, ext/soap, the stream layer among others</li>
   </ul>
   <p>Several under the hood changes also require in depth testing with existing
    applications to ensure that any backwards compatibility breaks are minimized.</p>
   <p>The current <a href="http://wiki.php.net/todo/php53">release plan</a> expects
    a stable release sometime around the end of Q1 2009.</p>
  </div>
 </content>
</entry>


