<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>TestFest 2009</title>
  <id>http://www.php.net/archive/2009.php#id2009-05-09-1</id>
  <published>2009-05-09T21:45:38+02:00</published>
  <updated>2009-05-09T21:45:38+02:00</updated>
  <category term="frontpage" label="PHP.net frontpage news"/>
  <link href="http://www.php.net/index.php#id2009-05-09-1" rel="alternate" type="text/html"/>
  <link href="http://www.php.net/archive/2009.php#id2009-05-09-1" rel="via" type="text/html"/>
  <content type="xhtml">
    <div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
      <p>
        TestFest is upon us once again. For those who don't know, this is the
        time of year where User Groups and individuals donate a little of their
        time and effort to increasing the test coverage of PHP.
      </p>
      <p>
        Hundreds of thousands of lines of code are working in concert to
        assemble one of the simplest to learn and fastest running scripting
        languages in the business. All this is achieved with the expectation
        that very few bugs will make it into releases and the ones that do
        will be stomped out quickly, efficiently and will never be heard from
        again. This is a lofty goal and is only possible through a system of
        tests designed to continuously evaluate the well-being of PHP.
      </p>
      <p>
        This year the QA Team has been very busy implementing new features
        and improvements to make the TestFest experience easier and more
        enjoyable than ever before. Some these improvements include a
        Subversion repository for test storage and tracking, a Virtual
        Machine for simple test environment setup, and improved documentation
        of testing procedures.
      </p>
      <p>
        2009 is looking to be the most successful TestFest event ever. Over
        20 User Groups spanning Belgium, Brazil, Catalonia, Canada, France,
        Germany, Ireland, Italy, Netherlands, Norway, Peru, USA and the UK
        have already registered. This is an incredible response and we still
        have 2 months left to go.
      </p>
      <p>
        Getting involved couldn't be simpler. Visit the
        <a href="http://qa.php.net/testfest.php">QA TestFest page</a> to
        find out how you can organize a TestFest event in your community.
        We are looking forward to seeing your communities tests being
        committed into PHP.
      </p>
    </div>
  </content>
</entry>
