<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:default="http://php.net/ns/news">
  <title>php|tek 2009</title>
  <id>http://www.php.net/archive/2009.php#id2009-02-20-1</id>
  <published>2009-02-20T18:59:30+01:00</published>
  <updated>2009-02-20T18:59:30+01:00</updated>
  <default:finalTeaserDate xmlns="http://php.net/ns/news">2009-05-19</default:finalTeaserDate>
  <category term="conferences" label="Conference announcement"/>
  <link href="http://www.php.net/conferences/index.php#id2009-02-20-1" rel="alternate" type="text/html"/>
  <link href="http://www.php.net/archive/2009.php#id2009-02-20-1" rel="via" type="text/html"/>
  <content type="xhtml">
    <div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
      <p>We are happy to invite you to this year's php|tek conference, to be held <abbr title="2009-05-19" class="dtstart">May 19</abbr>-<abbr title="2009-05-23" class="dtend">22, 2009</abbr> in <span class="location">Chicago, Illinois</span>, and hosted (as always) by the folks at php|architect.</p>
      <p>Join us to hear talks and tutorials on a variety of PHP subjects from PHP experts such as Ed Finkler, Sara Golemon, Chris Shiflett, Sebastian Bergmann, Derick Rethans, Stefan Priebsch, Christian Wenz and our mid-conference keynote by Andrei Zmievski on PHP6. You can see the full schedule at <a href="http://tek.mtacon.com/c/schedule">http://tek.mtacon.com/c/schedule</a> - we guarantee you won't be disappointed.</p>
      <p>This year we are also happy to invite you to our Unconference and Hack-a-thon which will be held in the early evenings, separate from the main schedule. You'll have a great time and won't miss a thing! This, coupled with our entertaining evening events and multiple networking opportunities will prove to make your trip to the conference an educational and memorable one!</p>
      <p>Early bird pricing is in effect until February 28, 2009 so hurry to take advantage of this offer before it's too late!</p>
      <p>For details on the conference, including registration and hotel information, please visit us at <a href="http://tek.mtacon.com/" class="url">http://tek.mtacon.com/</a>.</p>
    </div>
  </content>
</entry>
