<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>2009 PHP TestFest</title>
  <id>http://www.php.net/archive/2009.php#id2009-07-09-1</id>
  <published>2009-07-09T10:04:07+02:00</published>
  <updated>2009-07-09T11:09:53+02:00</updated>
  <category term="frontpage" label="PHP.net frontpage news"/>
  <link href="http://www.php.net/index.php#id2009-07-09-1" rel="alternate" type="text/html"/>
  <link href="http://www.php.net/archive/2009.php#id2009-07-09-1" rel="via" type="text/html"/>
  <content type="xhtml">
    <div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
     <p>
      So finally we are at the end of the
      <a href="http://wiki.php.net/qa/testfest">2009 PHP TestFest</a>.
      It has been an outstanding success with the
      <a href="http://gcov.php.net/PHP_5_3/lcov_html/">coverage increasing</a>
      by about 2.5% overall and 887 new tests contributed in the TestFest SVN
      repository of which 637 have already been added to PHP CVS.
     </p>
     <p>
      <a href="http://wiki.php.net/usergroups">User groups</a> from all
      over the world have worked hard to make this happen and we thank
      <a href="http://results.testfest.php.net">each and every one of you</a>
      for your contribution to PHP!
      You really made a difference to the PHP5.3 release quality.
     </p>
     <p>
      There still are few loose ends to tie up - the
      <a href="http://testfest.php.net/repos/testfest/">TestFest SVN repository</a>
      will be <em>closed</em> for contributions later this week and the last few
      tests will be moved into the main PHP repository. Finally, we have
      <a href="http://www.flickr.com/search/?w=all&amp;q=elephpants&amp;m=tags">10 elePHPants</a>
      and <a href="http://www.flickr.com/search/?w=all&amp;q=testfest+mug&amp;m=tags">9 TestFest mugs</a>
      to give out. The winners of mugs and elePHPants
      will be drawn at random from a list of people who wrote tests;
      the winner's names will be announced later this month.
     </p>
     <p>
      For those that would like to continue to make a difference by
      writing tests there are two options. You can simply continue by
      submitting new tests to the <a href="http://php.net/mailinglists">QA mailing list</a>,
      or, if you have written a significant number of tests you might
      consider applying for your own
      <a href="http://php.net/cvs-php">PHP CVS (or SVN) ID</a>.
      In your application you should reference the tests that you have
      written in support of your application.
     </p>
     <p>
      Last but not least, we would  like to thank all of the
      companies and institutions that sponsored TestFest.
      These include Combell, Faculdade Impacta de Tecnologia, IBM,
      iBuildings, Itera, Mayflower, Microsoft, Nexen (Alter Way Group), php|architect,
      Redpill-Linpro and Zend.
     </p>
    </div>
  </content>
</entry>
