<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:default="http://php.net/ns/news">
  <title>International PHP Conference</title>
  <id>http://www.php.net/archive/2010.php#id2010-09-25-1</id>
  <published>2010-09-25T13:09:54+02:00</published>
  <updated>2010-09-25T13:09:54+02:00</updated>
  <default:finalTeaserDate xmlns="http://php.net/ns/news">2010-10-11</default:finalTeaserDate>
  <category term="conferences" label="Conference announcement"/>
  <link href="http://www.php.net/conferences/index.php#id2010-09-25-1" rel="alternate" type="text/html"/>
  <default:newsImage xmlns="http://php.net/ns/news" link="http://phpconference.com/" title="International PHP Conference 2010">ipc2010.gif</default:newsImage>
  <link href="http://phpconference.com/" rel="via" type="text/html"/>
  <content type="xhtml">
    <div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
     <p>Not just another conference - this year has seen some high-valued
     conferences (like our IPC Spring Edition in Berlin) and we are already
     preparing the next big PHP conference. But this year makes a difference.
     It's the 10th. anniversary of the International PHP Conference. Being in
     business for ten years, we met some great people, made true fans and
     encouraged PHP developers all over the world to commit their passion for
     web-development to a growing community, that is behind some of the most
     well-known websites today.</p>
     
     <p>Of course, a great event is nothing without great developers and we are very
     happy to welcome the PHP community to our next International PHP Conference
     2010! Again, this conference is packed with workshops, sessions and keynotes
     on some of the most trending topics in PHP and web development today. Wether
     you are the developer dealing with core PHP features, the project lead that
     is in continuous integration or the CTO looking for professional solutions,
     this conference is the place to be. Not because of our 10 years of
     experience in bringing together some of the most experienced heads in PHP
     development - but because of this conference being one of Europe's leading
     technology events that have been made possible by a really passionate
     community. And that is ... by you.</p>
    </div>
  </content>
</entry>
