<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:default="http://php.net/ns/news">
  <title>PHPNW12 - PHP North West 2012</title>
  <id>http://www.php.net/archive/2012.php#id2012-08-21-1</id>
  <published>2012-08-21T19:59:32+02:00</published>
  <updated>2012-08-21T19:59:32+02:00</updated>
  <default:finalTeaserDate xmlns="http://php.net/ns/news">2012-10-05</default:finalTeaserDate>
  <category term="conferences" label="Conference announcement"/>
  <link href="http://www.php.net/conferences/index.php#id2012-08-21-1" rel="alternate" type="text/html"/>
  <default:newsImage xmlns="http://php.net/ns/news" link="http://conference.phpnw.org.uk/phpnw12" title="PHPNW12">phpnw12_details_200x1441.png</default:newsImage>
  <link href="http://conference.phpnw.org.uk/phpnw12" rel="via" type="text/html"/>
  <content type="xhtml">
    <div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
     <p>
      Organised by developers for developers,
      <a href="http://conference.phpnw.org.uk/phpnw12">PHPNW12</a>
      is the perfect opportunity to learn, network and mix with peers and
      industry leaders, as well as discover the latest tricks, techniques
      and innovations in PHP and internet development.
     </p>
     <p>
      Come to Manchester and join in this year's fabulous
      <a href="http://conference.phpnw.org.uk/phpnw12">PHPNW conference</a>.
      Building on the success of previous years, we have a bigger schedule,
      more venues, more great content and hopefully more fun than ever!
      With speakers from across the PHP sphere and its allied technologies,
      there is something for everyone at this event, and always someone to
      talk tech to if you want to.
     </p>
     <p>
      Starting on the Friday with our
      <a href="http://conference.phpnw.org.uk/phpnw12/tutorial-day/">Tutorial Day</a>
      which is a fantastic opportunity for individuals and teams of PHP
      developers to come together for a full day of hands on teaching tailored
      just for you. Whether you want to know more about Building a Zend
      Framework 2 Application, Tools of the PHP Trade, Hands on debugging with
      Xdebug, Test your code like a pro – PHPUnit in practice, Create your own
      PHP Extension step by step or Scaling Your Team Using HubFlow – A Git
      Workflow For Git Hub, this will be the experience for which you have
      been waiting.
     </p>
    </div>
  </content>
</entry>
