<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:default="http://php.net/ns/news">
  <title>International PHP Conference Spring 2015</title>
  <id>http://php.net/archive/2014.php#id2014-11-05-1</id>
  <published>2014-11-05T22:31:52+01:00</published>
  <updated>2014-11-05T22:31:52+01:00</updated>
  <default:finalTeaserDate xmlns="http://php.net/ns/news">2015-06-10</default:finalTeaserDate>
  <category term="conferences" label="Conference announcement"/>
  <link href="http://php.net/conferences/index.php#id2014-11-05-1" rel="alternate" type="text/html"/>
  <default:newsImage xmlns="http://php.net/ns/news" link="https://phpconference.com/2015se/en" title="International PHP Conference Spring 2015">ipc2015.png</default:newsImage>
  <link href="https://phpconference.com/2015se/en" rel="via" type="text/html"/>
  <content type="xhtml">
    <div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
	<p>The International PHP Conference is a globally recognized event for PHP developers, webworkers, IT managers and everyone interested in web technology.</p>
	<p>Once again, the conference will explore key topics and core technologies for developers and decision makers. We will show you how to scale your applications, explain the details of Continuous Integration or evaluate different approaches to NoSQL. Attendees will have the opportunity to meet with speakers, core developers and consultants, and there are often opportunities to evaluate your code. Community and enterprise projects profit from our international reputation and impulses given from the developer community.
	</p>
	<p>
	    Below is the information for our Call for Papers, the deadline is November 24th, 2014:
	</p>
	<p>
	    We are already planning for the IPC Spring 2015 which will take place
	    in Berlin again. We hope that next week's
	    conference will give you some inspiration for new talks for the next
	    conference. 
	</p>
	<p>
	    We are very much looking forward to your submissions for workshops,
	    sessions &amp; keynotes, which can be either in English or in German. Our
	    goal is to provide at least 60% of the whole program of the integrated
	    conference in English, so that our international friends have plenty
	    of sessions to choose from. Please see below our list of topics which
	    we would like to have covered, but please feel free to add additional
	    topics, if you believe they fit into the scope of the conference.
	    We are looking forward to your exciting submissions and wish you all
	    the best!
	</p>
	<p>
	Basic facts:
	<ul>
	    <li> Date: June 7th - 10th, 2015 </li>
	    <li> Location: Berlin</li>
	    <li> Deadline for Submissions: November 24th, 2014</li>
	    <li> URL for Submissions: <a href="conftool.sandsmedia.com">conftool.sandsmedia.com</a> </li>
	</ul>
	<br/>
	Topics:
	<ul>
	    <li>Core PHP /PHPNG</li>
	    <li>PHP Frameworks</li>
	    <li>PHP Scaling &amp; Performance</li>
	    <li>PHP Security</li>
	    <li>PHP Testing &amp; Quality</li>
	    <li>HHVM &amp; Hack</li>
	    <li>Architecture</li>
	    <li>JavaScript / ECMAScript 6</li>
	    <li>JavaScript  Frameworks</li>
	    <li>JavaScript Performance &amp; Security</li>
	    <li>Web APIs &amp; Services</li>
	    <li>Agile</li>
	    <li>Continuous Delivery</li>
	    <li>DevOps</li>
	    <li>Cloud</li>
	    <li>Data Stores</li>
	</ul>
	</p>
	<p>
	    We are looking forward to your proposals!
	    For inquiries and suggestions, please do not hesitate to contact us!
	    Yours, 
	    The Program Team of the International PHP Conference 
	</p>
    </div>
  </content>
</entry>
