<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:default="http://php.net/ns/news">
<title>PHPeste 2023</title>
<id>https://www.php.net/archive/2023.php#2023-10-06-1</id>
<published>2023-08-10T11:00:00-03:00</published>
<updated>2023-08-10T11:00:00-03:00</updated>
<link href="https://www.php.net/conferences/index.php#2023-10-06-1" rel="alternate" type="text/html"/>
<link href="https://phpeste.org/" rel="via" type="text/html"/>
<default:finalTeaserDate xmlns="http://php.net/ns/news">2023-10-05</default:finalTeaserDate>
<category term="conferences" label="Conference announcement"/>
<default:newsImage xmlns="http://php.net/ns/news" link="https://phpeste.org/" title="PHPeste 2023">phpeste_400x120.png</default:newsImage>
<content type="xhtml">
  <div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
    <p>
      <strong>About the Conference</strong>
    </p>

    <p>
      Introducing <a href="https://phpeste.org/">PHPeste</a>, a distinguished PHP conference, championed by the
      resilient communities of Brazil's Northeast. Over the years, this event has graced cities including João Pessoa,
      Salvador, São Luis, Recife, Natal, and once again returns to the coastal beauty of Fortaleza.
    </p>

    <p>
      Spanning two enriching days, attendees can anticipate:
    </p>

    <ul>
      <li>
        <strong>Comprehensive Learning:</strong> Dive deep into the world of PHP through hands-on sessions and
        workshops.
      </li>
      <li>
        <strong>Networking Opportunities:</strong> Engage with passionate PHP enthusiasts and professionals who embody
        the spirit and vigor of the Northeast.
      </li>
      <li>
        <strong>Expert Speakers:</strong> Gain insights from an array of top-tier industry speakers, sharing their
        expertise and experiences.
      </li>
    </ul>

    <p>
      PHPeste is a collaborative effort by communities from various Northeastern states, including Alagoas, Bahia,
      Ceará, Maranhão, Paraíba, Pernambuco, Piauí, Rio Grande do Norte, and Sergipe. This year, the
      "<a href="https://phpcomrapadura.org/">PHP com Rapadura</a>" community takes the helm, ensuring that the event
      remains both high-quality and accessible. Thanks to the tireless efforts of our volunteer members, we are able to
      provide an exceptional experience at a cost-effective price, making this conference accessible to many.
    </p>

    <p>
      <strong>Date: October 6-7, 2023 in Fortaleza, Ceará.</strong>
    </p>

    <p>
      <strong>
        Location: Estácio University Center of Ceará, ESTÁCIO VIA CORPVS | R. Eliseu Uchôa Beco, 600 Guararapes,
        Fortaleza, Ceara, Brazil.
      </strong>
    </p>

    <p>For more information about the event, visit the website:
      <a href="https://phpeste.org/">PHPeste</a>
    </p>
  </div>
</content>
</entry>
