<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>Statement on glibc/iconv Vulnerability</title>
  <id>https://www.php.net/archive/2024.php#2024-04-24-1</id>
  <published>2024-04-24T18:40:29+00:00</published>
  <updated>2024-04-24T18:40:29+00:00</updated>
  <link href="https://www.php.net/index.php#2024-04-24-1" rel="alternate" type="text/html"/>
  <link href="https://www.php.net/archive/2024.php#2024-04-24-1" rel="via" type="text/html"/>
  <category term="frontpage" label="PHP.net frontpage news"/>
  <content type="xhtml">
    <div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
	 <p>Recently, a bug in <b>glibc</b> version 2.39 and older (<a
	 href="archive/entries/2024-04-24-1.xml">CVE-2024-2961</a>) was uncovered
	 where a buffer overflow in character set conversions *to* the
	 ISO-2022-CN-EXT character set.</p>
     
	 <p>This specific buffer overflow in glibc is exploitable through PHP,
	 which uses the iconv functionality in glibc to do character set
	 conversions. Although the bug is exploitable in the context of the PHP
	 Engine, the bug is not in PHP. It is also not directly exploitable
	 remotely.</p>
     
	 <p>There are numerous reports online with titles like "Mitigating the
	 iconv Vulnerability for PHP (CVE-2024-2961)" or "PHP Under Attack". These
	 titles are misleading as this is *not* a bug in PHP itself.</p>
     
	 <p>Currently there is no fix for this issue, but there is a workaround
	 described in <a
	 href="https://rockylinux.org/news/glibc-vulnerability-april-2024/">GLIBC
	 Vulnerability on Servers Serving PHP</a>. It explains a way how to remove
	 the problematic character set from glibc. Perform this procedure for every
	 gconv-modules-extra.conf file that is available on your system.</p>
     
	 <p>Additionally it is also good practice for applications to accept only
	 specific charsets, with an allow-list.</p>
     
	 <p>Some Linux distributions such as <a href="GLIBC Vulnerability on
	 Servers Serving PHP">Debian</a>, CentOS, and others, already have
	 published patched variants of glibc. Please upgrade as soon as
	 possible.</p>
     
	 <p>Once an update is available in glibc, updating that package on your
	 Linux machine will be enough to alleviate the issue. You do not need to
	 update PHP, as glibc is a dynamically linked library.</p>
     
	 <p>PHP users on Windows are not affected.</p>
     
	 <p>There will therefore also not be a new version of PHP for this
	 vulnerability.</p>
    </div>
  </content>
</entry>
