<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>Dutch PHP Conference 2024 - Call for Papers</title>
  <id>https://www.php.net/archive/2023.php#2023-10-30-1</id>
  <published>2023-10-30T09:08:22+00:00</published>
  <updated>2023-10-30T09:08:22+00:00</updated>
  <link href="https://www.php.net/conferences/index.php#2023-10-30-1" rel="alternate" type="text/html"/>
  <link href="https://www.phpconference.nl" rel="via" type="text/html"/>
  <finalTeaserDate xmlns="http://php.net/ns/news">2023-12-17</finalTeaserDate>
  <category term="cfp" label="Call for Papers"/>
  <newsImage xmlns="http://php.net/ns/news" link="https://www.phpconference.nl" title="Dutch PHP Conference">DPC-logo.png</newsImage>
  <content type="xhtml">
    <div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
      <p>We are thrilled to announce the return of the <strong>18th edition</strong> of the <a href="https://phpconference.nl/">Dutch PHP Conference</a> in 2024! Join us for an exciting in-person event, set to take place from <strong>March 12 to March 15, 2024</strong> at Pathé Noord Amsterdam. :elephant::tada:</p>
      <p>We’re on the lookout for exceptional, technical, and non-technical sessions from speakers who can delve into advanced topics, spark creativity, and captivate our live audience.</p>
      <p>In the past, we’ve had remarkable speakers covering a wide range of subjects within the PHP ecosystem, including frameworks, DevOps, architecture, JavaScript, scaling, testing, performance, and security. We’re eager to build on these themes for this year’s in-person conference.</p>
      <p>But that’s not all - we also invite speakers to explore non-technical topics that play a crucial role in the success of developers and development teams. These can encompass communication, interpersonal skills, relationships, self-management, and even the business and economics aspects of development. In other words, the soft skills that complement deep technical expertise, as well as the broader environment essential for the success of technical developers.</p>
      <p>This invitation is intentionally open-ended, aiming to inspire everyone to share their ideas, insights, and hard-earned experiences in the vast realm of development in which we all thrive.</p>
      <p>The <strong>
        <a href="https://sessionize.com/dpc24">Call for Papers</a>
      </strong> is now open and will remain so until <strong>December 17, 2024</strong>. We can’t wait to hear from you!</p>
  </div>
</content>
</entry>
