<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:default="http://php.net/ns/news">
  <title>ConFoo Montreal 2025: Call for Papers</title>
  <id>https://www.php.net/archive/2024.php#2024-08-15-2</id>
  <published>2024-08-15T14:31:26-04:00</published>
  <updated>2024-08-15T14:31:26-04:00</updated>
  <link href="https://www.php.net/conferences/index.php#2024-08-15-2" rel="alternate" type="text/html"/>
  <link href="https://confoo.ca/en/2025/news/cfp-open-2025" rel="via" type="text/html"/>
  <default:finalTeaserDate xmlns="http://php.net/ns/news">2024-09-22</default:finalTeaserDate>
  <category term="cfp" label="Call for Papers"/>
  <default:newsImage xmlns="http://php.net/ns/news" link="https://confoo.ca/en/2025/news/cfp-open-2025" title="ConFoo Montreal 2025">confoo_2024.png</default:newsImage>
  <content type="html">
	  <p>ConFoo is a multi-technology conference specifically crafted for developers. With over 150 presentations, offered by local and international speakers, this conference wish to bring outstanding diversity of content to expand developers knowledge, increase productivity and boost skills.</p>

	  <p>Want to share your knowledge and expertise to hundreds of experts in your field? Want to be part of our talented team of renowned speakers? Want to demonstrate how human intelligence is changing our field of work?</p>

	  <p>The team at ConFoo is looking for speakers and talk proposals for its 2025 event in Montreal. From PHP Framework to best practices and other related technologies, ConFoo is renowned for the quality of its program, and you could be a part of it!</p>

	  <p>Our conferences are both dynamic and educational and are set to help participants build on their career. We usually recommend a 45-minute format, including a 10 Q&amp;A session at the end. Checkout last year conference schedule to get an idea of what you can expect.</p>

	  <p>You have until September 22 to <a href="https://confoo.ca/en/2025/call-for-papers">submit your proposal on our website</a>.</p>

	  <p>Until October 18th, participants can enjoy a <a href="https://confoo.ca/">300$ discount</a> on their registration! </p>
  </content>
</entry>
