<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>Drupal Mountain Camp 2024</title>
  <id>https://www.php.net/archive/2024.php#2024-01-05-1</id>
  <published>2024-01-05T10:08:42+00:00</published>
  <updated>2024-01-05T10:08:42+00:00</updated>
  <link href="https://www.php.net/conferences/index.php#2024-01-05-1" rel="alternate" type="text/html"/>
  <link href="https://drupalmountaincamp.ch" rel="via" type="text/html"/>
  <finalTeaserDate xmlns="http://php.net/ns/news">2024-03-07</finalTeaserDate>
  <category term="conferences" label="Conference announcement"/>
  <newsImage xmlns="http://php.net/ns/news" link="https://drupalmountaincamp.ch" title="Drupal Mountain Camp 2024">drupalmountaincamp-2024-banner.png</newsImage>
  <content type="xhtml">
    <div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
      <p>
        We are thrilled to announce the 4th edition of <strong>Drupal Mountain Camp</strong>, taking place from March 7th to March 10th, 2024, in Davos, Switzerland.
      </p>

      <p>
        <strong>About the Conference</strong><br/>
        Featuring seven different tracks (three parallel), focusing not only on Drupal but also on Symfony, Laravel, PHP, modern JavaScript (React), as well as accessibility,
        diversity, and inclusion, the conference will be a great opportunity to learn, connect, and share with the community.
      </p>

      <p>
        Drupal Mountain Camp brings together experts and newcomers in web development to share their knowledge in creating interactive websites using Drupal and
        related web technologies. We are committed to unite a diverse crowd from different disciplines such as developers, designers, project managers as well as
        agency and community leaders.
      </p>

      <p>
        <strong>Winter Wonderland in Davos</strong><br/>
        Embrace the beauty of the Swiss Alps during the snowy season.<br/>
        Enjoy <strong>social activities</strong> like skiing, snowboarding, sledding, and indulging in traditional fondue high up in the mountains.<br/>
        It's not just a conference; it's an adventure!
      </p>

      <p>
        <strong>Who should join?</strong><br/>
        Although the conference is predominately focused on Drupal, this years' edition we've expanded to several non-Drupal tracks, thus we invite everyone related to PHP or the modern web to participate.
      </p>

      <p>
        Davos is located high up in the Swiss alps, reachable from Zurich airport within a beautiful 2 hours train ride up the mountains.<br/>
        <ul>
          <li>Date: March 7 - 10, 2024</li>
          <li>Location: Davos, Switzerland</li>
          <li>Language: English</li>
        </ul>
      </p>

      <p>
        <strong>Interested?</strong><br/>
        Submit a session, register as a participant, or become a sponsor today.<br/>
        Keep in touch via our website at: <a href="https://drupalmountaincamp.ch" target="_blank">drupalmountaincamp.ch</a>
      </p>
    </div>
  </content>
</entry>
